[{"answer": "No, anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "She'll open", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What did she say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Isn't that against the law", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Wow", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Oh! I can't believe this, my friend! I've been wanting to get one of these things! Are you sure... Are you sure you can't use one of these things?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "It's got an alarm that beeps", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh no. I got all my appointments up here.", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh! I can't believe this, my friend! I've been wanting to get one of these things! Are you sure... Are you sure you can't use one of these things?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Where'd you get this", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Something huh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "She looked great. She asked about you", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah she asked for your number, I think she's gonna get in touch with you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I got no problem with that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Now I should tell you at this point she's under the impression the you are a....", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A marine biologist", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "A what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "A marine biologist....why am I a marine biologist", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I didn't think it was a job", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, it's just her sense of humor.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What is that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "OK I'll see you later.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "There you are", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "There you are", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "So", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "So what do you have to say for yourself?", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So what do you have to say for yourself", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why should I have anything for say for myself", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Please", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What, how did you know that", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You know when my friend saves someone no one asks if he's trying to hit on her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well you're not my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hey that's my purse!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No that's a radio.", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "No that's a radio.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Marine-Biologist.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "No I wasn't.    ", "qsentId": 38}]